A Guide to the John Skelton Williams Papers, 1884-1926
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- 1892-1926
  - 1899-1946 - Newspaper Clippings
    - Scrapbook of Newspaper Clippings re Seaboard Air Line Railway 1904-1905 (Box 87)
    - Scrapbook of Newspaper Clippings re Seaboard Air Line Railway 1905-1908 (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1906, 1 item. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1908, 1 item. (Box 87)
    - Scrapbook of Newspaper Clippings re Seaboard Air Line Railway 1908-1910 (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1910, 3 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings 1911, 1 item. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1912, 3 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1914, 9 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings 1914, 2 items. (Box 87)
    - Magazine 1914, 1 item. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1915, 63 items. 2 folders. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings 1915, 14 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1916, 7 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings 1916, 10 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1917, 2 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings 1917, 2 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1918, 6 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings 1918-1919, 21 items. 3 folders. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams' confirmation 1919, 9 items. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1919, 1 item. (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams' confirmation 1920, 35 items. (Box 88)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1920, 22 items. 2 folders. (Box 88)
    - Newspaper clippings 1920, 48 items. 3 folders. (Box 88)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1921, 49 items. 2 folders. (Box 88)
    - Newspaper clippings 1921, 4 items. (Box 88)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1921, 12 items. (Box 88)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1922, 5 items. (Box 89)
    - Newspaper clippings 1922, 31 items. (Box 89)
    - Magazines 1922, 5 items. (Box 89)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1923, 1 item. (Box 89)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams 1924, 2 items. (Box 90)
    - Newspaper clippings 1924, 1 item. (Box 90)
    - Newspaper clippings 1946, 1 item. (Box 90)
    - Newspaper clippings related to Williams n.d., 72 items. (Box 90)
    - Newspaper clippings n.d., 190 items. 3 folders. (Box 90)
  - 1900-1926
    Photographs, Greeting Cards, Biographical Sketches.
    - Portriat photograph of John S. Williams [ca. 1906], 1 item. (Box 91)
      Used in Men of Mark in Virginia.
    - Photograph of John S. Williams (top, far right) and unidentified individuals n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Photographs of John S. Williams n.d., 2 items. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of John S. Williams and William McAdoo n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Negatives of John S. Williams and unidentified individuals n.d., 3 items. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of Advisory Board of Director General McAdoo; John S. Williams (bottom, second from left) n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of Delphi n.d. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of Unidentified Individuals n.d. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of John S. Williams with his family n.d. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of Mrs. John S. (Lila) Williams n.d., 2 items. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of Mrs. John S. (Lila) Williams n.d., 2 items. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of John S. Williams, Jr. 1901, 1920, 1921, 1922, n.d., 31 item. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of John S. Williams n.d., items. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of John L. Williams n.d., 2 items. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of Williams McAdoo n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of M. B. Mount n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of Jacquilin Taylor n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of F. Q. Brown n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of unidentified individual n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of unidentified individual n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of unidentified building n.d., 1 item. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of Greece n.d., 2 items. (Box 91)
    - Photograph of Greece n.d., 47 items. (Box 91)
    - Invitations, Greeting Cards, etc. n.d., ca. 98 items. (Box 92)
    - Invitations n.d., 36 items. (Box 92)
    - Calling Cards n.d., ca. 125 items. (Box 92)
    - Calling Cards, Invitations, etc. n.d., ca. 105 items. (Box 92)
    - Invitations, Greeting Cards, etc. n.d., 17 items. (Box 92)
    - Invitations, Programs, etc. n.d., 22 items. (Box 92)
    - House Calendar 1905, 1 item. (Box 92)
    - Pamphlet: "The Causes of Our Agricultural Depression" by John S. Williams n.d., 1 item. (Box 93)
    - Greeting Cards, Invitations, etc. n.d., 12 items. (Box 93)
    - Invitations, Postcards, etc. n.d., 15 items. (Box 93)
    - Greeting Cards, Calling Cards, etc. n.d., 31 item. (Box 93)
    - Postcards n.d., ca. 80 items. (Box 93)
    - Postcards n.d., ca. 60 items. (Box 93)
    - Tooth X-ray 1916, 1 item. (Box 93)
    - Biographical sketches of John S. Williams n.d., 13 items. (Box 93)
  - Letterbooks 1899-1922
    - Letterbook 1899 Jan. -June, 1 item. (Box 94)
    - Letterbook 1899 July-1900 Jan., 1 item. (Box 94)
    - Letterbook 1899 Oct. -Dec., 1 item. (Box 95)
    - Letterbook 1900 May-Sept., 1 item. (Box 96)
    - Letterbook 1900 Aug. -Oct., 1 item. (Box 97)
    - Letterbook 1901 Feb. -April, 1 item. (Box 9)
    - Letterbook 1901 April-July, 1 item. (Box 99)
    - Letterbook 1901 July-Aug., 1 item. (Box 100)
    - Letterbook 1901 Oct. -Dec., 1 item. (Box 101)
    - Letterbook 1901 Oct. - 1902 Jan., 1 item. (Box 102)
    - Letterbook 1902 Feb. -March, 1 item. (Box 103)
    - Letterbook 1902 June-1903 Feb., 1 item. (Box 104)
    - Letterbook 1902 Aug. -Dec., 1 item. (Box 104)
    - Letterbook 1902 Dec. -1903 April, 1 item. (Box 105)
    - Letterbook 1903 April-Sept., 1 item. (Box 105)
    - Letterbook 1903 Sept.-1904 Feb., 1 item. (Box 106)
    - Letterbook 1904 Jan. -April, 1 item. (Box 106)
    - Letterbook 1904 July-Sept., 1 item. (Box 107)
    - Letterbook 1904 Sept. -Dec., 1 item. (Box 107)
    - Letterbook 1905 Jan. -March, 1 item. (Box 108)
    - Letterbook 1905 March-June, 1 item. (Box 108)
    - Letterbook 1905 May-1906 June, 1 item. (Box 109)
    - Letterbook 1905 Aug., 1 item. (Box 109)
    - Letterbook 1905 Aug. -Nov., 1 item. (Box 110)
    - Letterbook 1905 Nov-1906 Dec., 1 item. (Box 111)
    - Letterbook 1906 April 7-June 16, 1 item. (Box 112)
    - Letterbook 1906 June-Aug., 1 item. (Box 112)
    - Letterbook 1906 July-Dec., 1 item. (Box 113)
    - Letterbook 1906 Dec.-1907 May, 1 item. (Box 113)
    - Letterbook 1908 June 20-Oct. 1, 1 item. (Box 114)
    - Letterbook 1908 Oct.-1909 May, 1 item. (Box 114)
    - Letterbook 1909 May-Dec., 1 item. (Box 115)
    - Letterbook 1909 Dec.-1910 Feb., 1 item. (Box 116)
    - Letterbook 1910 June-1911 March, 1 item. (Box 117)
    - Letterbook 1911 Nov.-1912 May, 1 item. (Box 118)
    - Letterbook 1912, 1921, 1922, 1 item. (Box 119)
    - Letterbook 1918 Nov.-1919 March, 1 item. (Box 120)
    - Letterbook 1919 March 8-May 15, 1 item. (Box 120)
  - Scrapbook of clippings 1914-1919, 1 item. (Box 121)
    - Nine Design Plans for Formal Gardens at Morven (2 plans), Elk Hill, Stratford House, Bremo Recess, Valentine Museum, Appomattox, Graymont, and 1 Unidentified Home n.d., Oversize Photograph. (Box OS Box E-4)